Tufts Hillel Records UA244
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Born digital materials, circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002; 197 Digital Object(s) 197 digital objects comprising 5825 files.; 53 Gigabytes; .25 Linear Feet
  - tuftshillel_hillel-open-house_72157627640601612, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00135; 1 Digital Object(s); 29.8 Megabytes
  - tuftshillel_hillel-semi-formal_72157629099294316, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00136; 1 Digital Object(s); 104.2 Megabytes
  - tuftshillel_hillel-service-day_72157627707160553, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00137; 1 Digital Object(s); 3.5 Megabytes
  - tuftshillel_holocaust-survivor-elizer-ayalon-speaks-at-tufts-hillel_72157625319429726, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00138; 1 Digital Object(s); 75.7 Megabytes
  - tuftshillel_i-fest-2011_72157626525741506, UA244.002.00139; 1 Digital Object(s); 25.4 Megabytes
  - tuftshillel_immigration-lecture-sol-gittleman_72157628055709814, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00140; 1 Digital Object(s); 0.6 Megabytes
  - tuftshillel_john-saunders-lecture_72157628306500937, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00141; 1 Digital Object(s); 2.8 Megabytes
  - tuftshillel_merrin-moral-voices-distiguished-lecture-with-eric-schosser_72157632178454390, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00142; 1 Digital Object(s); 29.4 Megabytes
  - tuftshillel_michael-oren-lecture_72157629850724793, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00143; 1 Digital Object(s); 23.6 Megabytes
  - tuftshillel_miracle-martini-night-2012_72157632278570566, UA244.002.00144; 1 Digital Object(s); 43.7 Megabytes
  - tuftshillel_miracle-martini-night_72157628471410485, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00145; 1 Digital Object(s); 27.7 Megabytes
  - tuftshillel_moral-voices-welcome-julian-agyeman_72157631855190012, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00146; 1 Digital Object(s); 14.5 Megabytes
  - tuftshillel_newsletter_12_13_72157629247814463, circa circa 2013; UA244.002.00147; 1 Digital Object(s); 117.7 Megabytes
  - tuftshillel_out-in-israel-11-7_72157628080443844, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00148; 1 Digital Object(s); 3.5 Megabytes
  - tuftshillel_out-in-israel-shorty_72157628017411847, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00149; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.5 Megabytes
  - tuftshillel_personnel_72157626929494744, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00150; 1 Digital Object(s); 28.6 Megabytes
  - tuftshillel_purim-2013_72157632870921046, UA244.002.00151; 1 Digital Object(s); 21.2 Megabytes
  - tuftshillel_purim-party-2012_72157629209281604, UA244.002.00152; 1 Digital Object(s); 33.9 Megabytes
  - tuftshillel_rabbi-summit-fixing-the-world-series_72157631991359954, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00153; 1 Digital Object(s); 13.4 Megabytes
  - tuftshillel_race-4-rwanda_72157626488035586, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00154; 1 Digital Object(s); 101.6 Megabytes
  - tuftshillel_read-by-the-river_72157626139537701, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00155; 1 Digital Object(s); 149.1 Megabytes
  - tuftshillel_repair-the-world-dinner-11-7_72157627955155247, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00156; 1 Digital Object(s); 2.8 Megabytes
  - tuftshillel_repair-the-world-workshop-with-rabbi-will-berkovitz_72157628471854937, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00157; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.4 Megabytes
  - tuftshillel_ruttenberg-shoot_72157627640580700, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00158; 1 Digital Object(s); 17.6 Megabytes
  - tuftshillel_rwanda-program-10-27-11_72157627930975447, 2011; UA244.002.00159; 1 Digital Object(s); 1.6 Megabytes
  - tuftshillel_service-trip-to-adamah_72157626525999778, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00160; 1 Digital Object(s); 0.3 Megabytes
  - tuftshillel_sukkot_72157627970423786, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00161; 1 Digital Object(s); 3 Megabytes
  - tuftshillel_survivors-speak-an-evening-with-extraordinary-survivors-of-genocide_72157626039112741, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00162; 1 Digital Object(s); 63.6 Megabytes
  - tuftshillel_survivors-speak_72157629574049915, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00163; 1 Digital Object(s); 23.9 Megabytes
  - tuftshillel_tal-becker_72157627930937817, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00164; 1 Digital Object(s); 6.7 Megabytes
  - tuftshillel_the-berlin-experience_72157626010602279, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00165; 1 Digital Object(s); 94.3 Megabytes
  - tuftshillel_through-the-lens_72157632262190724, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00166; 1 Digital Object(s); 123 Megabytes
  - tuftshillel_tu-bshevat-sustainable-sunday-supper_72157626047712636, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00167; 1 Digital Object(s); 77.3 Megabytes
  - tuftshillel_tufts-hillel-alumni-happy-hour_72157625131055544, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00168; 1 Digital Object(s); 117.4 Megabytes
  - tuftshillel_tufts-hillel-alumni-philanthropic-initiative-session-1-11-27-2011_72157627930970835, UA244.002.00169; 1 Digital Object(s); 3 Megabytes
  - tuftshillel_tufts-hillel-semi-formal_72157626039119009, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00170; 1 Digital Object(s); 84.9 Megabytes
  - tuftshillel_tufts-in-argentina_72157628471465995, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00171; 1 Digital Object(s); 51.5 Megabytes
  - tuftshillel_tufts-in-rwanda_72157628309050163, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00172; 1 Digital Object(s); 47.2 Megabytes
  - tuftshillel_tufts-president-tony-monaco-visits-with-board-of-directors_72157627831475730, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00173; 1 Digital Object(s); 3.4 Megabytes
  - tuftshillel_unleavened-bread-around-the-globe-international-passover-seder_72157626525361828, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00174; 1 Digital Object(s); 11.3 Megabytes
  - tuftshillel_welcome-back-bbq-2010_72157624915300845, UA244.002.00175; 1 Digital Object(s); 39.4 Megabytes
  - tuftshillel_yisrael-neeman_72157632870926668, circa circa 2002 -- 2017; UA244.002.00176; 1 Digital Object(s); 8.1 Megabytes
  - Unprocessed digital materials, 2002--2009; UA244.002.002
    - Endowment Celebration and Neubauer Dinner, 2008; UA244.002.002.00001
    - Tufts Hillel "leading up North", 2007; UA244.002.002.00002
    - Tufts Hillel "leading up North", 2007; UA244.002.002.00003
    - Berlin photos, 2009; UA244.002.002.00004
    - Cabaret and Shabbat, 2007; UA244.002.002.00005
    - Rebuilding the North, 2007; UA244.002.002.00006
    - Transforming Community, 2004; UA244.002.002.00007
    - KZ Shabbat (originals), 2008; UA244.002.002.00008
    - Hillel Photos August-September 2007, UA244.002.002.00009
    - Hillel Photos October 2007, UA244.002.002.00010
    - Hillel Photos November-December 2007, UA244.002.002.00011
    - Bagel Brunch September 2004, UA244.002.002.00012
    - Hillel Photos Sukkah Building October 2004, UA244.002.002.00013
    - Nick Kristof February 2007 Photos, UA244.002.002.00014
    - Hillel Photos September 2003, UA244.002.002.00015
    - Joseph and Janette Neubauer Recognition Dinner 2008, UA244.002.002.00016
    - Hillel Photos 2002-03, 2002--2003; UA244.002.002.00017
    - Hillel Pictures October-November 2007, UA244.002.002.00018
    - Hillel Pictures From the Center 2004, UA244.002.002.00019
    - Hillel Photos August-September 2007, UA244.002.002.00020
    - Paul Rusesabagina Merrin Distinguished Lecture Series 2005, UA244.002.002.00021
- Rabbi Summit papers, circa 1979 -- 2018; UA244.003; 1.8 Linear Feet
  This series contains some restricted material. Restrictions related to specific material are listed in the detailed contents list. This series may require review before it is available for use. Please contact DCA for further details.
  Transferred by Tufts Hillel, 2018, accession UA-2019-016.
  This series is arranged by format.
  This series contains photographs and negatives documenting the construction of the Granoff Family Hillel Center, events held or attended by Hillel, and portraits of Rabbi Summit, as well as a VHS cassette titled, "Campus Under Siege." This series also contains subject and office files created or collected by Rabbi Summit during the course of his work as Jewish Chaplain and Director of Tufts Hillel. Files contain Tufts Hillel administrative material and material related to the broader Hillel organization; documentation of programs and events, including posters, calendars, and fliers; publications, including the Tufts Hillel publication "From the Center"; newsclippings; information on Judaic Studies courses; program reports and grant records; correspondence; and material related to the Granoff Family Hillel Center and its Ark.
  - Photographs, negatives, and video, circa 1982 -- 2002; UA244.003.004; .4 Linear Feet (Box 4)
    This file contains photographs and negatives documenting the construction of the Granoff Family Hillel Center, events held or attended by Hillel, and portraits of Rabbi Summit. This file also contains a VHS cassette titled, "Campus Under Siege."
  - Subject and office files, circa 1979 -- 2018; UA244.003.005; 1.4 Linear Feet 1 record container and one flat file (Box 5, Box Large Map Case 3 Drawer 3)
    This file contains some restricted material and may require review before it is available for use. Please contact DCA for further details. University records are closed for 20 years from the date of their creation. Records older than 20 years that do not pertain to student education, staff and faculty employment and Board of Trustees records are open for research.
    This file contains subject and office files created or collected by Rabbi Summit during the course of his work as Jewish Chaplain and Director of Tufts Hillel. Files contain Tufts Hillel administrative material and material related to the broader Hillel organization; documentation of programs and events, including posters, calendars, and fliers; publications, including the Tufts Hillel publication "From the Center"; newsclippings; information on Judaic Studies courses; program reports and grant records; correspondence; and material related to the Granoff Family Hillel Center and its Ark.